I get strong!
You get strong! We get strong!
Again!
I get strong!
You get strong! We get strong!
Salt. Brine.
Can you smell it?
Can you taste it?
That's the sea.
And that's where I belong.
Well, right now
you belong to me.
And you've still got
three more miles.
"Belong to you"?
Man, what kind of shit is that
to say to a Black man?
"Belong to you".
What?
That's some
slave shit there, man.
You're kidding, right?
Wha--
Yo, Coop,
are you fuckin' with me?
This ain't-- Dude, seriously,
this ain't funny if you--
You arefuckin' with me!
Fuck you.
I knew it.
Oh, that's so low.
- You put the hands up.
- That's so low.
I'm sorry.
Your face was worth it, though.
That is so unfair.
- You know how unfair that is?
- Your face!
Come on, baby! Last year
was your best year.
16 solo tackles, two sacks!
Let's go, baby!
That's it, that's it.
Get one, get one, get one. Yeah!
And then, looky loo,
here come the Oakland Raiders!
- Let's go, one more, come on!
- Dig, baby, dig!
- Eat! Eat!
- That's it, that's it.
One more. I need one more out
of you. One more, come on now.
- Who's watching? Who's watching?
- Come on.
Who's watching? Who's watching?
- Who's watching?
- Come on.
I get strong!
You get strong!
- Shut up! We get strong!
- We get strong! Ahh!
Come on, big-time.
- Come on!
- Come on, big-time.
Sometimes you gotta throw
some weight!
All right, all right!
Thanks for warming it up, baby!
Come on. Come on.
Who wants another ring?
You want another ring?
I want another ring.
Damn right you want another
ring. Just like JLo does.
Put some ice on that right now.
- Jenny from the block, baby.
- Here we go, come on.
- Let's go.
- Something like five assists.
- Something like three sacks.
- Yeah, that's the word.
It don't come easy, Corey.
It comes with more reps.
It comes with more work.
One more. Dig deep.
Come on, now. I get strong!
You get strong!
We get strong!
Come on now. Come on, come on.
There we go. That's it.
- That's it.
- Come on, Coach, your turn.
Hell no. I told you guys this
morning I'm not working out.
I already worked out
before y'all got here. I'm good.
- Do it for the Blacks.
- What-- Do it for the Blacks?
- Obama.
- Do it for Obama?
- Yeah, "Yes, we can".
- Yeah.
No, I can't.
All right...
I did not jump.
Baby,
you didn't not jump.
- Okay...
- Ah, yes...
That's what
I'm talkin' about, baby.
We have an entire table
of a massive feast,
and you're still making food.
That looks so good, Marquis.
Baby, did you reel that in?
- Did Ireel that in?
- Yeah.
Hey, don't worry, Paula.
We're gonna take him back out.
I'll make an angler
out of you yet.
Oh, thank you, Captain.
I cannot wait.
Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Willy Will!
What's up, baby?
Yo, Will.
Beer's in the cooler, man.
- Hey, bud.
- Hi.
Um, you got anything stronger?
Like tequila
or... battery acid maybe?
- Damn.
- You okay, bud? What's wrong?
Well, my days with Smith Barney
are finito.
Pink-slipped.
They let you go? Fuck!
- Sorry, man.
- Yeah. Yep.
Closing the entire office.
It's, uh...
Recession's killing everything.
I'm sorry.
Sorry to hear that.
Yeah, that's terrible,
Will. I'm sorry.
You know what? It's probably
for the best. Right?
Losing your job in financing
during a recession? It's better.
- I mean...
- It's better.
- It is better. Like, for real.
- Could be worse.
Things like that happen
for a reason. You know?
It really is.
Three teams, six years.
Yeah, man,
I was eight teams in four.
You'll be all right. Don't trip,
you'll land on your feet.
I'm on no... I'm on no teams.
Hey, Coop, if your other man
doesn't show up this weekend,
can we bring Willy Boy here
with us?
Yeah, maybe.
Crack of dawn Saturday? You down
for some deep-sea fishing?
Come on, let's go, baby!
Let's go, baby! Let's go, baby!
That sounds like a lot of fun.
Yes, thank you.
It's legit spiritual, man,
I swear.
I don't know what Corey's doing,
but I swear it's spiritual.
- Daddy!
- Whoa, whoa!
Dad.
Vuda!
You gotta keep your eyes
on your surroundings, okay?
I can't have that beautiful face
getting burned up on the grill.
Daddy, do fish cry
when they die?
Oh...
- Do fish cry?
- No. What? No, of course not.
Baby, they don't feel anything.
- They don't feel that?
- They don't. No, they don't.
Just...
You gotta, like, shake it
to make sure.
All right, straight
from Cooper's Hole...
No, no, no.
Can we not call it that, please?
Huh? I mean, it's a fishing hole
and I discovered it, so...
Cooper's Hole!
It's not like you don't know
what you're doing
with this little
play on words, guys.
I dunno what you mean. Corey,
do you have a problem with it?
- Cooper's Hole!
- No?
Why are you
saying it like that?
Will, how about you?
Straight from the bottom
of Cooper's Hole?
Ooh, baby, that looks delish.
I'd love some of that...
meat from that hole.
No. I am on the record.
I am not putting anything
in my mouth
that came from a hole
with your name on it.
AWakey-wakey, eggs and bakey!
Oh, you guys look hot.
- Oh, wait...
- Get outta here!
- No, no. Keep looking at me.
- Get outta here, you pervert.
Oh, yeah.
Keep talking shit to me.
Sick fuck. Get out.
Out. Stop.
- Will! Why?
- Open the door!
Why?!
Okay, food for a few days.
Water for a week.
Beer for a month.
Hey, how many beers per person
before you're an alcoholic?
How many sandwiches
is that?
That's 40. That's 40 sandwiches.
That's 40 fucking sandwiches?
Yeah, I got 20 fuckin' PB&J and
20 fuckin' turkey and cheese.
How did you make 40 sandwiches
so fast?
I have explosive speed.
Yeah. That's why
you're in the NFL right now.
A girl can dream.
Nope. No, she can't.
'Cause you bullhorns
won't let her sleep.
- Mama.
- You. Why are you here?
I love you.
Holy shit!
What hobo did you roll for that?
Uh, my mom bought me this, okay?
LL Bean. Full price.
Because she cares.
Sorry, sir, I can't hear you
over that jacket - it's so loud.
- Please.
- Okay, do you guys want coffee?
Nah, we're good, thanks, babe.
- Do you want breakfast?
- Ah, no. I mean, I wish.
But we promised Cooper
we'd be there by 5:00, so...
Did you take Dramamine?
Oh, er, the thing about that,
Paula, is, uh...
Dramamine is for pussies.
Here, take Dramamine.
If I can find it.
- I was fine last week, babe.
- Babe...
Babe, you don't get less ill
from motion sickness.
- It just gets worse.
- I'm gonna be just fine.
Well, what time
are you heading back?
I don't know.
Probably very late.
Well, the weather's not supposed
to be great.
We're gonna be all right.
We're four big, strong men.
Well, you can't bench-press
the ocean.
- The safest.
- Mm-hm.
Get out. Go.
- I love you.
- Cool jacket.
That's the boat?
- Hey, yo! Morning, boys!
- It's tiny.
Y'all ready?
Deep sea awaits!
We all gonna fit?
It's supposed to hold 11 people.
Dwarf or normal adult-sized?
Come on, let's get it, baby!
Wake your ass up!
- All right. Get the coolers.
- You've combed your hair, Nick.
You still look sleepy.
Good mornin', Bassmaster.
About ready to roll?
Yeah,
just give me a minute.
Uh...
what the fuck is that?
Uh, this is a gift from my mom.
My bad. It's nice.
Shut the fuck up.
I didn't realize you guys
were packed already.
Yeah.
Yeah, the moving
company's coming tomorrow.
It's such a pain in the ass
dealing with this shit
every year.
Bro, I would straight-up trade
with you right now.
My life for yours.
What, you wanna
move to Oakland?
I would move to the moon if
it meant I got to play pro ball.
Yeah...
There's no water there.
No water on the moon?
In Oakland.
Er, yeah, except for that, uh,
San Francisco Bay thing
they got out there.
I meant fishing water.
They got an estuary there,
but that's that pure fishing,
standing-still bullshit.
What's wrong with that?
I need the waves, man.
I need the movement,
the open air, the ocean.
I used to, uh...
As a kid, I used to wander
down to the Sonoran Desert,
outside of Gilbert.
And shit was terrifying, man.
Just nothin'.
But nothin' everywhere I looked.
And I just... felt it out there.
- You know?
- Felt what?
All of it.
You know, whatever "it" is.
It's just...
Just felt it.
And I get that same exact shit
whenever I'm out on the water.
Are you talking about
being alive,
or God, the universe, what?
I mean, I dunno if
it's all that. It's just like...
Honestly, it's...
Shit, honestly, I really don't
even think about it that much.
You know? 'Cause I feel like
I might fuck it up if I pay
too much attention or...
...study it, you know,
I'm gonna lose it.
I just know it. You know,
when I feel it, it's there.
It's like...
It feels like I'm at peace.
You know, it feels like home.
All right.
Let's go.
You get up there,
I'll pass you up some shit.
Oh, shit.
- Are you okay?
- Yep.
Oh, you ain't gonna make it
through this one.
Hey, Willy Boy... Cooper's Hole!
Can we stop
calling it that?
Somebody woke up early
to see Daddy off.
Cooper's Hole!
Vuda... Vuda...
Come up here. Oh!
Now, what are you doing awake?
Where are you going, Daddy?
- Ah...
- Do not say "you know what".
Or I'll get questions all day
about fish D-Y-I-N-G.
Um...
I am going on a, uh...
A play date.
But I promise I'll be back
later, okay, Vuda?
Okay, Daddy.
It'll probably be late, though.
Um, last night with the guys.
Okay. Just remember
the movers are coming early.
All right.
Okay, now, you better
be good for Mama, okay?
Okay, Daddy.
I don't wanna hear about you
causing any trouble. Mm-hm?
I love you.
Don't forget Mama.
Mm-mm.
Love you, Mama.
Love you.
Love you too.
Breakfast time, stink?
Oh, the back seat
is too small for me.
You all right?
Yeah, my leg fell asleep
back there.
I want shotgun next time, Corey.
Oh, yeah...
Oh, Marquis,
it's freezin', dawg!
It'll warm up
when the sun comes up, man.
You reckon
we'll hit a lot of chop?
Uh, probably.
I want to get out there
before this front rolls in.
What, weather?
Ah... a storm.
But it's cool. We'll be done
by 3:00 or 4:00, back by dusk.
Figured that weather
doesn't come until late.
- What's this for?
- Cellphones.
Seasalt can fry your phone.
Plus, we ain't gonna
have any service
once we get a few miles out.
Cool. Okay.
That's... a good idea.
Hey, you got some room
in your bag, too?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's some in the front.
Stick 'em all at the front.
Hey, um...
you got a radio, right?
Oh, damn, a radio.
Nah, but I think
we got two tin cans,
a long-ass piece of string.
That should work, though, right?
Will's a little
worried about the boat.
Come on, man.
Yeah, I got a radio, Will.
All right, sorry.
You nervous?
You worried about my boat?
My small, tiny boat, where you
can feel every small bump?
- All right, yep. Got it, thanks.
- Little waves?
- A school of fish swimming by?
- All right.
You got three big men
to keep you safe.
Yep.
We're gonna have a good time,
Will, I promise you.
...with a very
powerful cold front
moving in, moving down the east,
what we meteorologists refer to
in fancy terms
as an "upper air disturbance",
is coming to the Gulf and that's
going to bring a major storm--
Hey, it's Nick, leave a m--
Nicholas. Uh, it's Mom.
I know you went out fishing
this morning.
I just wanted to make sure that
you had seen the weather report
about this big storm
that's supposed to hit.
Call me when you get this,
will you, sweetie?
Love you, hon. Bye.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Stuart, it's me.
Have you heard anything
from Nick?
No. Why?
Well, I know he went out fishing
this morning with the guys,
and there's this big storm
that's supposed to be
hitting us later.
I called him, but it went
right to voicemail.
Um... just call me
if you hear from him, okay?
Yeah. I'll give him a call now.
Oh! Look at this haul.
Every time. Key, why are we
leaving this spot?
Bruh, you know
the fish at Cooper's Hole, man.
Will, I'm telling you -
beautiful fish.
Really beautiful,
but a horrible name.
Dude. Was that with the Bucs?
2002.
You won the big one
with Brad Johnson as your QB?
And Chucky as a coach
and the baddest defense
on the motherfuckin' planet.
- Better than the Ravens?
- Man, fuck B-more.
Okay.
You didn't want to let him,
uh, propose first?
Hey, who's this?
It's gotta be a cushion cut,
three-and-a-half carat
pink diamond!
I think it's kinda sad
that you still remember that.
It was traumatic.
Uh... that was my ex.
I'm like less than a year
into dating her
and she's asking me
for a $75,000 ring.
Yeah, and that's why
she's your ex.
And, oh, by the way,
what signals was I sending
about wanting to get married?
Ah. Women don't need signals,
just hints.
- The smallest of little things.
- Which makes it my fault.
Oh, man,
it's alwaysyour fault.
Sooner you figure that out,
the better off you'll be.
Yeah, honestly,
you should just take the blame.
Every time. From the jump.
Is that what you guys do?
- Nah.
- Nah, nah, not me.
No.
- ♪ I'm so fly ♪
- ♪ So fly ♪
- ♪ So cool ♪
- ♪ So fresh ♪
- ♪ I'm so smooth ♪
- ♪ So smooth ♪
Hey, just think of all those
times you made us puke
during hard workouts, Nick.
Not now.
Tried to tell you -
motion sickness only gets worse.
Why can't we just stop
and drop lines here?
Man up, Nick.
Cooper's Hole awaits!
Whoo!
♪ You know that I'm
a cheap ho man, but I groove ♪
♪ Drop-damn fresh from the grill
to the shoe ♪
♪ My pocket full of nuts ♪
♪ And my neck full of juice... ♪
Let's drop.
- Corey, you get the anchor, man?
- Yeah.
Keep the tripline
tight, let it out easy.
I'm not losing another anchor
like last weekend.
I got you.
Nick, you need to
lie down. You look like shit.
I'm sorry
I said Dramamine's for pussies.
Oh, got it.
Are you all right, man?
- Got it!
- Feeling a little better?
Oh, shit.
Jeez, dude,
you just put your line in.
- Woo-hoo!
- Nice.
Will, that's how you get a fish.
You see that, boy?
- Yeah. No, I know.
- Yeah.
How are you feeling?
How's your... how's your "it"?
I'm big Corey,
that's little Corey.
Hey, don't put my shit
in air quotes, man.
It's your shit, now, is it?
My zen, motherfucker.
Or whatever you wanna call it.
Man, I shouldn't even have
told you about that shit.
Mm.
Oh. I got... I got one too.
- Oh, it's a big one.
- Nah, I think that's the boat.
I dunno. It's movin'.
You're literally connected
to the boat.
- Yeah, that's the boat.
- Yeah, loosen it up.
All right.
I gotta do better.
- Better how?
- I don't know.
Ah.
Yeah, it gets you thinking
out here, doesn't it?
- Yeah, it does.
Shit, okay, all right.
So, wait, back to "better how".
I mean, I just... I think...
...a lot of my life
I've been selfish, you know?
And... distant.
All right. Um...
So what?
You know, so have I.
You know, it's fuckin' do-or-die
every year for motherfuckers
like me and Corey, man.
And every time we're out there,
survival mode.
Gotta think about surviving,
surviving... It's-it's...
You know, it's fuckin' selfish.
'Cause I don't care about
nobody else out there.
I don't give a shit about any of
the other players. It's just me.
There's 53 spots on the team -
I need to get one.
I need to make one,
whatever I gotta do. You know?
Run fast, make plays,
hit motherfuckers,
knock somebody out.
You know,
fly down as a gunner.
Whatever the fuck I gotta do,
I gotta make the team,
keep the playbook.
And it sounds fucked up, but...
- That's not fucked up.
- ...but it's true.
It's not fucked up.
That makes perfect sense.
To me it does, anyway.
I can't think about
anything else
but what's directly in fucking
front of my view.
You know, that man across
from you, beating him out,
because if I do,
if I... if I...
I don't know, if I take
my mind on something else,
it takes my mind
off of surviving.
Distance?
Selfish? No.
Gotta focus on me.
Survive.
And that's it.
Hey, man, this weather
is not looking good.
- Yeah, yeah, nah, you're right.
- Like, real not good.
Hey, uh...
hey, we gotta wrap it up soon.
Shit, we gotta wrap it up now.
That's easy for me.
Hey, Corey,
you get that anchor up, man?
- Yeah, I got you.
- Appreciate you.
- Shit, my fault.
- You got it.
Yep.
Punch me that end, man.
- This goes underneath?
- Yeah, yeah.
What the fuck?
The anchor's stuck.
Well, come on,
big man, put smoke on it.
Hey, what the fuck
you think I'm doing?
All right, hold it.
I can't lose another anchor.
Hold on. Hey, Will.
Will, help us up here.
I got you. Wait. Just keep
that slack in the line.
- All right.
- Get in here.
Hey, Schuyler.
- All right.
Hey, uh, maybe some of that
motivational shit, Schuyler?
All right! Here we go!
I get strong!
You get strong!
We get strong!
I get strong!
You get strong!
We get strong!
- Okay, okay.
- Ah, fuck, fuck.
Okay, okay, all right.
I don't think we have much
daylight left. I'm just saying.
All right, all right,
I'm gonna try something. Corey.
Corey, tie it up right there.
Port side cleat.
Right, everybody hold on
to something.
This is my best idea
but it's worth a shot.
All right.
Okay, let's see if this works.
I'm not cutting it.
All right, all right,
just hang on.
- This might buck and roll a bit.
- Got it, got it, got it.
All right, take it easy,
take it easy.
Easy, easy, easy!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Easy!
- Hold on.
A little more, Coop.
A little more.
Yeah.
I think it's working!
Hey, it's working!
Is it working?
Marquis, should we cut it?
Hit that shit, Coop.
Hit that shit.
Whoa, whoa!
Coop!
It's not budging, stop!
Whoa, man, whoa!
- I got full.
- Go again.
Go, go, go!
Full throttle!
- Oh, shit!
- Stop, Coop, stop!
- Stop, man, stop!
- Get to the top! Get to the top!
What happened?
Coop!
Get on the boat!
Get back to the boat!
Get to the boat,
get to the boat.
Get back to the boat.
Get back...
Damn.
Go, go, go, go!
What happened?
What the fuck happened?
You guys okay?
Okay, okay. We got it,
we got it. Everybody on.
- Come on, Coops!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's think
for a second.
You push up, we'll push down.
Come on!
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, let's rock it.
We gotta get some kind of
rhythm. Like a teeter-totter.
Okay.
Get on the other side.
Get on the other side
of the boat.
We'll push it now. We'll flip
it. We'll flip. Yeah, yeah.
All right. Stay together.
All together.
I get strong!
You get strong!
We get strong!
It's not working!
We're wasting muscle power!
Forget about it.
Wait.
Wait. The line!
- Will...
- Hey, cut the anchor line!
The anchor's holding us down!
We cut the line and it'll flip.
- I'll get the line.
- With what? Our teeth?
I got it!
Got it!
I'll cut it on the boat.
I'll cut it on the propeller.
Oh, Will. Hold on.
- Got it?
- Ah, shit...
Yeah!
Yes, baby!
We'll take this line...
and we'll tie it...
to the side.
And pull... pull this
motherfucker and flip...
flip the boat.
...making landfall
a little after midnight,
moving through Sarasota
and slipping over
to St Petersburg,
before hitting the Tampa area.
We're expecting Category 2 winds
in what is currently classified
as a tropical cyclone...
Hey, it's Nick.
Leave a message.
Babe, it's me.
Call me
when you're back in range.
This storm looks pretty serious.
I hope you guys
are on your way back in.
I love you. Talk soon.
...storms like these
are unpredictable--
We're never gonna flip
this fuckin' boat.
All right, fuck that.
I'm persistent, all right?
- But that shit ain't happening.
- Yeah, yeah, fuck that shit.
What do we have on the boat?
We have coolers.
We have food and water
in the coolers.
Yeah, they still
should be bungee'd down there.
Where are the lifejackets?
Yeah, yeah, the...
left... left of the console.
Okay. Hang tight.
Wait, wait.
If you open the hatch...
Oh, it's freezing.
It could flood the compartment,
sink the boat even more.
This is so fucked!
The boat can sink anyway,
no matter what.
Look, we can go awhile
without food,
but we need those vests now.
All right. On it, Corey.
Fuck.
Now what the hell are you doing?
- I can't fuckin' swim.
- What?
- No, he's right.
- No, no, no, no.
That's a bad idea, Will.
Guys, this is a really bad idea.
I need to fuckin' swim.
This shit just takes on water.
Y'all crazy.
Yeah, you need to stay warm too!
We need those vests, Nick.
Now what?
- Close it, close it.
- No, no, no, close it, close it!
No, no, no, no! No, no!
Close it, close it!
No, no, no, close it, close it!
Come on, baby! Come on!
No, no...
It stopped. It stopped.
He got them!
- Here.
- Good job, man.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
There's more down there.
- Just give me a second.
- I got it.
You okay?
- Bro, is this it?
- All right.
What else we got down there?
Ah... flares.
I got flares down there.
Okay.
- I'll go get 'em.
- Where?
I'll get 'em.
Yes! Fuck yes!
- Come on!
- Yes!
Take 'em, take 'em.
I got 'em, I got 'em, I got 'em.
All right, now...
just... food and water.
- Food and water.
- What about the coolers?
They're down there.
I'll go, I'll go.
All right, they're on
the port side.
Oh, hell no!
I can't see nothing!
It's too cold, it's too cold.
No, I ain't going back.
Somebody else gotta do it.
- Are you doing it right?!
- I'm trying!
Help!
Hey! Over here!
They saw us.
They're coming back.
Turn around!
- You think they saw us?
- They're coming back.
They're coming back, though.
They're coming back.
They saw us, right?
They saw us.
Jesus Christ...
Now we're fucked.
They had to have
seen the light.
They saw us, right?
They saw us.
We gotta
get to the coolers.
Assuming they haven't
flooded yet.
My backpack.
The cellphones!
They're in the backpack.
It's in the centre console,
right by the steering wheel.
Yeah, they should...
they still should be there.
Just take a minute...
Take a minute to get my breath.
Just warm up a little bit.
Then I'm gonna go.
Hey, Corey.
What's worse?
This?
Or going oh and 16
in Detroit last year?
This is probably
the one and only time
that I'd like to say
I'd rather be in Detroit
right now.
No. I do love Detroit. I do.
That's very advanced.
- Yeah.
- Great.
And they were
doing other things,
of course, being,
you know, sisters.
Doing both... I'd say call it.
And they'd put head-to-head.
And they'd push on each other's
head, back and forth.
Oh, that's hilarious.
You're drawing
green hearts, aren't you?
And what are you drawing?
- A cat?
- Let me see that cat.
Oh, cute. Cute!
Oh!
Hello?
Hey, Marcia. It's me.
Hi, sweetheart. How are you?
I'm fine. I'm just, um...
a little worried
about Nick and the guys.
Wait, they're not back yet?
No. And this storm is--
Have you heard anything
from Nicky today?
No, I haven't. And I've
called him quite a few times.
Okay. I don't like this.
Um...
I tried to call him this morning
right after they'd gone out,
but it went
right to his voicemail.
Me too.
- Just now?
- Yeah.
I have felt weird all day.
I've just had this sensation
that something was off.
Stuart hasn't heard from him
either, I don't think.
I think we should call someone.
Yes, Nick!
Oh, you got it.
I got the...
Come on.
How are we gonna keep these dry?
Really fucking carefully.
Dude. Make sure you keep 'em
in the bags.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Whose is this?
That's mine.
Whose is this? Whose is this?
- That you?
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Turn on,
you piece of shit.
- I got nothing.
- Yeah.
- I got nothing yet.
I got nothing.
Me neither.
Come on!
I thought 911 was supposed
to be, like, everywhere!
Isn't there like a satellite
thing? Or what the fuck?!
I got Sprint.
Signal's usually pretty strong.
Except for now
'cause 4 is fucked. Okay.
Bro, that storm's
gonna be right over us
in half an hour.
All right, shut 'em down,
pack 'em up.
If none of us has service, we're
gonna be burning our batteries.
Central Dispatch,
this is unit 3-13, come in.
Go ahead, 3-13.
That call in
on those overdue boaters,
I've got an abandoned
Dodge Ram pickup truck out here
with an empty boat trailer.
License plate - one, one, Alpha,
seven, two, Echo, Charlie.
Copy, 3-13.
One, one, Alpha,
seven, two, Echo, Charlie.
Running that registration now.
Standby.
All right, look...
We might have some men
out on the open water.
Let's alert the Coast Guard.
Copy that, 3-13.
Coop! Coop!
Get back the boat.
Fuckin' storm!
- Coop!
- Come on.
Coop!
Marquis!
- Nick, here. Nick.
- Give me your hand.
Take the phones.
- I got the phones.
- Come on.
Hey, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
So fucking cold.
That's a good sign.
It means your core temperature's
still up.
Listen,
no one's going anywhere, okay?
I get strong, you get strong,
we what?
- We get strong.
You're goddamn right we do.
We're right here. I got you.
Ah.
Ah. Ah.
Yeah...
Raining's stopped, yeah?
- Yeah!
- Yeah, fuck that storm.
Oh.
Oh, thank Christ.
Good.
What the hell is that?
You hear that?
What is that?
What... what is that?
Here! Over here!
Corey!
Where the fuck are you?
Where's the boat?
I can't see anything.
I see the hull!
Here! I got the boat!
I got the boat! Here!
- Come on, come on!
- Oh, my leg! I'm cut!
I'm cut. I'm bleeding.
Coast Guardians,
what's goin' on out there?
Sir, just got
a report of a trailered vehicle
at the Seminole Boat Ramp
in Clearwater.
The only one left in the lot.
Pinellas County Sheriff
just called it in.
Any distress signals
tonight? Maydays?
No, sir.
No? AIS beacons? EPIRBs?
No, nothing.
That storm...
has been moving inland
since this afternoon.
What's the temperature like
out there?
Probably
in the low 60s on the water.
Inthe water?
52 degrees
at the moment.
This cold front's
like a snowplow.
Slices right through
the warm air
and pushes it up and out,
which makes the storm seas
that much worse.
All right, everybody stay up.
Let's go on Alert.
Let's monitor
the AIS frequencies
and the emergency beacons.
Get on Channel 16
and start making call-outs,
see if anybody responds.
This is about to
get real fucked,
real fast.
Come on, Nick, come on.
Yo!
This is gutcheck time now! Hey!
All right? And this is where
it's all goin' down!
All right?
All we gotta do
is kill the clock.
We ain't gotta score big,
we ain't gotta make no big stop.
All we gotta do
is grind this shit out.
All right?!
Dude! Key!
Get your head
in the fucking game, baby!
Come on, we got this!
Marquis!
You hear him?
Fuckin' hear him?
Listen, man...
Listen. Listen.
There's something...
happening to me.
This slide inside.
I can feel it.
I don't want to hear this. Dude.
I don't want to fucking hear
those words, Marquis.
Come on.
If it goes down here,
this is where it's supposed
to happen, you know.
Salt. Brine.
The sea.
Distance... Selfishness...
It's survival.
Survival.
No.
I don't want to hear that shit, okay?
You're making it through.
We're all making it through.
Vuda can see you, bro.
- Vuda...
- She's not here.
She's not here, man.
No, stop! Stop!
Coop! No, no, no, no!
- Dude, they ain't here!
- Not here!
It's okay!
It's okay, she's not here.
Ah! You're okay.
We're okay.
What's happening to him?
Hypothermia.
He needs body heat.
He needs heat. We gotta...
We gotta get around him.
And we'll pop this last flare,
fuck it.
Come on, man. Come on.
Watch his head,
watch his head.
Come on, watch his head.
Oh, it's... Come on, brother.
Hey. It's me again.
I'm getting worried,
I'm not gonna lie.
The sheriff said Marquis's truck
was the only one
left in the parking lot.
I really hope you guys
are getting drunk somewhere.
Please just call me.
Your mom's worried too.
Anything?
No. I just left him
another message.
Hey, Paula. It's Rebekah Cooper.
Hey, Rebekah.
Have you heard from Marquis?
Um... no.
And his truck is still there
at the Seminole boat launch.
I heard.
Have you heard from him
at all today?
No. I mean, they're staying out
because we're leaving.
He told me it might go late.
It's just, uh...
It's just weird that his phone
wouldn't be on, you know?
Yeah, I haven't heard
from Nick either.
Okay. Well, um...
four big, strong guys.
No need to panic,
I'm sure everything's fine.
Um... I'm gonna call
the Coast Guard all the same.
Okay, well, um...
stay positive.
If I hear from Marquis,
I'll give you a call.
You do the same
if Nick calls you, okay?
You bet.
Thanks.
- She know anything?
- No, nothing.
I know.
- It's okay.
- Right?
Yeah. Just waiting.
- Waiting.
- Yeah.
Hey, Coop. Come on, man.
You okay?
Let's look alive, bro.
Come on. Let's get you up here.
Calm down! Calm down, Coop!
What are you doing?!
You're losing it, man!
Will, you all right?
Stop saying shit
like that. It's in the past.
Come on. It's in the past.
- That was a shock.
- You all right?
Yeah. He got me good.
Let me go...
Let me go.
Will, get his legs!
Coop!
Chief,
a Rebekah Cooper called.
She said her husband Marquis
and his friends
went into the water earlier.
She hasn't heard anything
from them since.
Who were the other men?
Um... William Bleakley,
Nick Schuyler and Corey Smith.
Marquis Cooper's truck was found
out at the Seminole Boat Ramp.
Cooper and Smith?
They were Bucs.
Former football players.
How big was their vessel?
A 21-foot Everglade.
So we've got four men,
above average in size,
in a smaller boat, in the middle
of a giant fucking storm.
How far out of the Gulf
did they go?
The woman said
their fishing spot's
about 70 miles off the coast.
Jesus Christ.
When was sundown?
It was a little after 6pm,
but we have no
EPIRB beacons triggered
or any distress calls.
Anything on 16?
No, nothing.
You know, there's probably
nothing worse...
...than dying of hypothermia.
Drowning, by comparison,
is peaceful.
A few moments of panic and...
poof, you're pretty much gone,
but...
...hypothermia, that's a whole
different kind of shitshow.
And for people
who are in fantastic shape,
with very little body fat, like
professional football players,
it's even worse.
Once that body temperature
goes below 95 degrees,
which is only three degrees
below normal,
your veins start to constrict
in order to supply your heart
with blood,
which, by the way,
is already completely poisoned
by the sea water.
Motor functions fail.
Your speech starts to slur.
And your lungs
begin shutting down.
And that lack of oxygen
causes hallucinations,
dementia, rage.
And eventually,
it breaks your mind in half.
What do you
want to do, sir?
Let's upgrade their status
from Alert to Distress.
And if anybody bitches, you
tell them to call me directly.
Let's get the HC-144
and the Jayhawk rotoring up.
We need to get 'em
in the air immediately
because the weather's
turning ugly fast.
And call Mrs Cooper, see if
she's got some kind of a GPS,
maybe a written record of her
husband's favorite fishing spot.
- Roger that, sir.
- All right, go. Let's go.
Coop! Hey!
Come here. Come here.
Open your mouth. Drink the rain.
Coop, open your mouth
and drink the rain.
Hey, his heart's beating
out of his chest.
Mine too.
What does that mean?
Are we dying?
- I dunno.
- No, no one's dying.
No one's dying.
Can't go on like this,
man. Can't go on.
Can't go on like this, man.
Here, drink the water,
here, here, here. Here.
All right. Okay.
- We got this.
- We good. We good. We good.
I've got almost zero visibility.
We're gonna have to fly
instruments only.
I can't even see the water.
0-9-0, any visibility?
Negative, 6-5-0-5. Recommend
we lower our flight ceiling.
Roger that, 0-9-0.
Let's get some light down there.
Just watch your NVG's, lower
the flight ceiling to 1500 feet.
Alright. Go.
No, no, Rebekah, I'm on the way.
I'm on my way.
I'll be there soon.
Hey. What's going on?
The Coast Guard
called me back.
They changed their status
to Distressed.
This is now a fucking
rescue mission, Paula.
Oh, my God.
What are we looking for?
Um... uh, Marquis's old GPS.
It'll have the coordinates
to that, um... fishing spot.
Goddammit! Where is it?!
It's okay.
I'm gonna help you look.
I just hate this feeling.
I know. I do too.
But I'm gonna remember what you
said and I'm gonna remind you.
Four strong guys, no panicking,
stay positive.
- Okay?
- Okay, I'm trying.
I know you are.
Okay, what does it...
what does it look like?
- Anything on the cells?
- Nothin'.
And it's unlikely
they're in range
with the water the way it is.
The wind is blowing due west,
which is farther out to sea.
- What's the weather doing?
- The storm has made landfall
and the temperature
is staying in the 50s.
- Anything from our aircraft?
- They're saying no visibility
and they're spooked
about this weather.
They fly into fucking funnel
clouds, get 'em on the horn.
This is ASRT Jumbo.
Anybody got a visual?
Negative, Jumbo. Nothing here.
ASRT Dagger,
ASRT Dagger.
This is Command. Come in, over.
Command, this is ASRT Dagger,
I read you.
Copy that, Dagger.
This is Captain Close.
What have you got eyes on?
A whole lotta nothing, Captain.
Wind shear's clocking in
at 80 miles per hour
and everyone's ass
is starting to pucker up here.
Radar is completely useless.
The swells are too big.
The storm's knocked out
our radar
and infrared systems too and
it's shaking the shit out of us.
Okay, what's your
honest assessment?
We need a target to hit, sir,
or this is a needle
in a needle stack.
Be lucky to cover
half the search span
and we're gonna have to ground
if this weather doesn't abate.
Copy that.
Anything?
No. No.
Is that a phone?
Is that your phone?
Hello? Hello, yeah,
I can hear you. Go ahead.
Have you been able
to locate anything
that might tell us where
your husband was fishing?
No, not yet. Um...
Nick Schuyler's fiancee Paula
is here, helping me look.
Okay, listen, my aircraft
aren't going to be able
to stay up in this weather
much longer, Mrs Cooper.
But I do want to give you
as much time as possible
to get me something, okay,
before I bring these guys
back in.
I understand.
Rebekah!
It says... it says Garmin.
Is this it?
Wait, wait, wait.
Captain Close, we got it,
we got it. Hang on! Power plug.
Power plug is there.
- Oh. Okay.
- Hang on.
Just gimme a sec. It's the GPS.
I need to power it up.
Almost there.
Okay, I'm not going anywhere.
Ah... Hold on.
Okay.
What have you got?
- Cooper's Hole.
- Yeah, that's it.
- Um...
- Got it?
Okay, um...
All right,
here we go, here we go.
27 degrees, 27 minutes,
8 seconds north.
83 degrees, 37 minutes,
52 seconds west.
Okay, hold on one second.
All right, we got 27 degrees,
27 minutes, 8 seconds north.
83 degrees, 37 minutes,
52 seconds west.
Got it.
There's a shipwreck
reported over there.
Rebekah, did your husband
ever mention
anything about a shipwreck
where he was fishing?
- Yes, yes! That's it! Yes!
- Okay, all right.
Let's route those coordinates
to our aircraft. All right?
Okay, thank you so much,
Rebekah.
We'll get back to you
as soon as we can.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Okay, we've got their position.
En route now, ETA five minutes.
Marquis!
Coop!
Corey Smith.
Talk to me, brother.
I'm hot. Why am I so hot?
You're not hot.
It's your mind messing with you.
Look at me.
Look at me. Breathe.
I'm right here.
We're gonna start getting
our asses kicked
out here pretty soon.
I can't see a fucking thing.
Descending 500 feet.
This is an absolute shitshow.
I can't see anything.
I'm right here.
Look at me. Breathe.
Breathe. Focus.
Wake up! Wake up! Hey!
- He's slipping!
- Hold on!
Marquis! No!
No!
Corey, stop.
I got you. I got you.
I got you.
Corey!
No one's afraid!
I'm not afraid!
I'm not afraid! I'm not afraid!
Passing over
those coordinates now.
It's a total blackout. I can't
even see the white caps.
We're going home, Nick!
Hey!
Hold on!
- Help us!
Heyyy!
ASRT Jumbo, what's your status?
ASRT Jumbo, presently
over the coordinates. No visual.
We're gonna have to
pop smoke soon.
Weather getting worse.
All right, Jumbo.
Let's call it.
Heyyy!
Here!
Seen us?!
ASRT Jumbo,
I think I just caught something
out of the corner of my eye,
a light of some kind -
can anyone confirm?
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Negative, Jumbo.
Goddammit.
I think the lightning
is refracting off the water.
We're gonna have to
climb out of this now.
It's getting too hairy.
Command, we're returning home.
All right, Jumbo,
bring it on home.
- Corey! Look! Look!
- Hey!
Hey! Hey!
No. No.
Hey!
Okay.
Thank you.
They had to call off the search
due to the weather.
They'll send the planes back out
once the storm clears.
Okay.
We have to believe
everything's gonna be okay.
They probably ran out of gas,
they're drunk somewhere.
You know, they're being stupid.
God, I hope so.
- Yeah.
- I really do.
I mean,
it's almost morning, so...
you know, whatever's going on
is gonna be a lot easier to
figure out in the light of day.
Yeah. You're right.
But I have this bad feeling
that I just can't shake.
Lieutenant.
Yes, sir.
Let's make sure to give
the families a heads-up.
The media's more than likely
monitoring our air
and the story is probably
taking shape.
And I don't want them reading
some random news report
and fearing the worst.
Sir, are we
amending the mission
to search and recovery?
No.
No, not yet.
We're gonna have daylight
on our side soon enough.
In fact, I want to turn
this thing up.
I'm gonna put
a big fucking boat on it.
Where's the Tornado?
Psst!
You asleep yet?
Yeah, deep REM,
and right now I'm banging
Megan Fox, so shut up.
That's for your shitty joke.
Okay, listen up.
We have a situation.
We are being diverted to St Pete
to search for a small boat.
Four-man crew, lost at sea,
possibly capsized.
Now, I want everyone's eyes
on the water.
Electronics
in weather this severe
are often faulty and unreliable
and nothing beats the eye
of a United States sailor!
All right, sailors, let's do our
jobs today and save some lives.
Corey!
If you can hear us,
come to our voices!
Fuck.
They're gone, Nick.
How...
How?
They were...
they were bigger than us.
Stronger than us.
Better than us.
And this thing still beat them.
We're not gonna make it
much longer, are we?
They had no body fat, Will.
It hurt 'em.
Look, I'm wearing
this big, stupid jacket
and these trackpants,
and it's soaked through,
but because they're on my skin
it's giving me
at least a little warmth.
What we gotta do, we gotta
get you wrapped up, man.
We gotta get a coat or
something, anything in the boat.
There's gotta be
something still in the boat.
I'm not diving again.
Then take my coat.
You can wear my coat then.
I'm not taking
your fucking coat.
Do something, man. I don't wanna
watch you freeze to death.
We'll fucking both
freeze to death
if I take your fucking coat.
- Shark! Shark! Fuck!
- Fuck!
- Up! Up! Quick! Up!
- Oh!
Go, go! Get up! Agh!
- Okay.
The bait locker's
down there... the cooler.
The bait locker.
They're just looking around.
We're bleeding like stuck pigs.
We'll be okay.
Can they swim under this thing?
No. No. They're just trying
to score fish, man.
Oh!
- Fuck!
- Will...
My sandwiches!
No, stop!
I can get it, I can get it.
Look out!
Oh, shit!
Fuck!
No. No.
The dumbest shit
keeps cycling through my mind,
and I don't know why.
Distract me.
I don't want to think about
these damn sharks right now.
My brother...
...told me once...
"..How do we know that the last
few seconds of our lives...
"..that last...
"..that last time
our brain fires...
"..doesn't just...
"..stretch out endlessly?
"And that's our eternity."
In reality,
it's all over in a few seconds.
Jesus Christ, man.
We'd better hope so.
When's the last time
you went to church?
I don't remember.
You an atheist now?
No, Will. I'm a fuckin' realist.
Why in the fuck would I pray to
a God that started all this shit
and then killed our friends
in the process?
Who would want
that kind of help? Huh?
You're mad?
You're goddamn right I'm mad!
And I'm gonna stay mad.
It's warm.
Just don't give up on God, man.
Don't do that.
Fuck!
I'm not giving up on anything.
I get strong.
You get strong.
We get strong.
I get strong. You get strong.
- I get--
- That's right.
- You--
- Right.
We get--
I get--
You get--
...four fishermen,
including two NFL players,
have been reported missing
after failing to return home
from a boating trip
late last night.
Family members reported
they went some 70 miles
- out into the Gulf.
- Oh, shit. It's out.
And Coast Guard officials
found their vehicle--
The Coast Guard has
suspended the search for now.
Oh!
My God.
They're gonna go back out
when the weather clears.
Oh, fuck that!
Marcia, where are you going?
We are finding our son
if I have to get on a goddamn
boat and do it myself.
I can't see shit, man.
Not a fuckin' thing.
Same. Too dark.
Let me tell you something, Best.
If this storm can bat a boat
this fucking big around...
...just imagine what those
poor fuckers are going through.
That's if they're still alive, man.
I just feel like Mother Nature
might be making a statement
to all mortal men right now.
Yeah? What's that?
"Fuck off."
My fucking fingers.
You good? You good?
You good?
Are we done for one second?!
You okay?
What are you doing?
- Take that.
- Why?
Tie yourself to the boat.
We have to stay connected
to the boat.
If we lose the boat
in the storm, we will die.
- That's a terrible idea.
- It's the only idea I got!
We'll drown.
We're gonna drown either way.
Okay. Okay.
Motherfucker!
Don't tell me
to calm down.
- My son is out there!
- Ma'am, you can't be--
Is there anybody here
who's in charge
who can say something
meaningful to me right now
and... and cut all this shit?!
You must be Mrs Schuyler?
- Are you the man in charge?
- Yes. I'm Captain Timothy Close.
The news said that you have
changed the search effort
to a recovery mission.
That was a reporting error,
I'm sorry.
Then why is there nobody
out there
looking for my son
and his friends?
Ma'am, we have
over 200 personnel
actively looking for your son
and those guys,
including a Coast Guard cutter.
But I cannot,
in good conscience,
put my pilots back up
in the air.
- But--
- Not with this bad weather.
I would knowingly
be putting their lives at risk.
And then what would I tell
their mothers?
How long is... how long is
this crap supposed to go on?
Another hour or so.
And then we're gonna
get right back at it. Okay?
Captain...
Is my son dead?
If he is, I want to know. Okay?
Right now.
And start dealing with it.
Is...
Is my boy dead?
Do you believe that?
You're his mother.
Do you honestly believe that?
My bones...
say he's still alive.
Well, then that's what he is.
And I want you
to hold that thought
and I want you to strengthen it.
And I'm gonna do everything
in my power
to prove that to you.
Okay?
Okay.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
- Over here!
- Ahh!
Hey!
They have to see us, right?
It's daylight.
How can they not see us?
You're fucking orange!
Heyyy!
How the fuck
are you not seeing us?!
Hey!
Help!
Help us!
Come back!
Fuck! Fuck you!
Just give me a fuckin' break!
We've been in the water...
...24 hours.
How much longer are they
gonna keep looking for us?
I don't know, man.
If we're gonna dive for food...
...we should do it now
while it's still daylight.
Okay.
All right.
- Hang on.
- No.
I can do it.
You'll never stay down there
with that shit on.
I'll take this stuff off, then.
Ah...
That looks really tasty.
Fibre.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Will!
Will!
Will, you're a goddamn legend.
Are you kidding me right now?
Drink up.
Fuckin'...
mustard-flavored pretzels.
I hate those.
I don't give a fuck if these
are ass-flavored pretzels
right now, bro.
You kiddin' me?
Oh, they're fucking so good...
Oh, fuck. Why have they
gotta be so fuckin' salty?
What kinda sick fuckin' joke?
Agh.
Wait.
Is that land?
What the fuck is that?
What the fuck isthat?
- Is that mine?
- No, it's mine.
But my fingers are fucked.
No fuckin' signal.
Fuck.
How do we know we're not just
hallucinating right now?
Since when do people
hallucinate the same thing?
It's been hours
since we've seen planes, man.
It's now or never.
We're not gonna make it
another night.
Nick!
Somebody help!
Oh...
Will, where is it?
Where did it go?
- Nick!
- Will!
Where's the boat?
Where's the fuckin' boat? Will!
Nick!
Will!
Will, get back to the boat!
Come on! Come on, motherfucker!
I knew it wasn't fucking real!
Will!
Will.
You okay?
Hey. Hey.
ASRT Jumbo, this is Command.
What are you seeing?
Roger, Command.
Still no visual to report.
But FLIR and RADAR have
been restored to functionality.
All right, copy that, Jumbo.
Get me Tornado.
Tornado, this is Command
on Channel 1-4. Copy?
Roger that.
This is Command to USS Tornado.
How are you faring
in this fight?
USS Tornado to Command.
We've got nothing yet.
Into our 66th
nautical search mile.
We're gonna stay out
till we lose the light.
All right, copy that, Tornado.
You're awfully quiet.
Hey, Will.
Hey, you all right?
Just... just thinkin'.
Thinking about?
Why this...
...boat hasn't sunk
all the way yet.
And what they...
And what they'll say
at my funeral.
I wonder if I'll even be there.
Don't say shit like that, Will.
Don't even think shit like that.
We've made it this far,
haven't we?
We can make it
the fucking rest of the way.
Shoulda married that girl, man.
Put a ring on her.
Cushion-cut...
...three-and-a-half carat
pink diamond...
I married her.
She gets mad about this trip...
...and makes me stay back.
And I'm not in this mess.
I'm at home.
With her.
Making babies.
Fuck yeah, man.
That's right.
You think about that.
We can make that work. You just
gotta work with me, okay?
Okay?
You gotta hold on
just a little bit longer.
Can you...
What?
- What?
- Can you...
Can you just...
Can you tell my parents...
I'm not telling
your parents shit, Will.
You're gonna tell 'em yourself.
Tell... tell my mom...
Tell my mom...
What the fuck are you saying?
Tell her I'm...
Hot.
Hey.
Will, hey...
Warm...
- Just getting warm.
- Stop it.
Will...
Will, stop it.
- Just getting warm.
- Will. No.
No.
Son of a bitch!
You're not gonna fuckin'
do this! Not right now!
Not right now!
The storm's getting worse.
Get the fuck up here.
Go. Dammit.
Stop taking this shit off.
I love you!
Do you understand? We're fucking
brothers. Do not die!
Fuck! Will!
Come on, Will!
I need you to work.
I need you to fucking work!
Will!
You have to lift your legs up!
Please!
Will!
Fuck!
Sir, both aircraft
are heading back.
Hey, I want to thank you all
for your hard work
these last couple of days.
And I know how
you're all feeling right now.
But we are not out of this yet.
Hope is the strongest thing
that we have.
It is the only thing
Now, I want you to put
your faith in the Good Lord
and pray that these boys
get found...
...and that we can bring 'em
home, safe and sound.
All right, boys.
They're calling it.
- Oh.
- We did what we could.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
That's it. Dismissed.
Sir.
Give it a few more minutes?
- I'm down, brother.
- Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Hey, it's Nick.
Leave a message.
Hey, it's me, calling again.
You're really late. Keeping us
in suspense here, huh?
I really hope you guys
are okay...
...and you're just out of range.
But I'm starting
to think that...
...I might never see you again.
That hurts.
That fuckin' hurts.
But...
You know, if you're out there
and it's just too hard
or you're... you're...
in too much pain...
...I understand.
And I'm gonna be okay.
I'm gonna be okay.
I mean it.
It'll take a second, but...
I'll eventually get there.
I had such a good time
with you, babe.
We laughed a bunch.
And, um...
God...
Thank you for that.
Thank you for your heart.
Absolutely gave you mine.
Come here.
I know...
...that he is still alive.
I can feel it.
I know that
he's still out there.
I've just been...
out here talking to him...
...and hoping that he can
hear me, wherever he is.
So...
...let's talk to him together, okay?
Okay.
Hey!
Oh...
Yeah, that's definitely someone.
- Holy shit.
- I think we got him, brother.
I got him, sir.
Let's go, let's go!
Sir, the Tornado's reporting
a possible sighting!
Let's get 'em on the horn.
Get our aircraft to those
coordinates right now.
Right now! Let's go!
Been waiting two days
for this, people.
Visual on the subject.
One adult male. Standby.
Is he alive?
Is he in the boat?
Is he out of the boat?
Come on, tell me something.
We got him?
Have we got him?
Standby, Lieutenant.
Getting that confirmation now.
Confirming,
one adult male on a capsized--
All right, well,
where are the other three?
We do not give up
on those other three.
Subject acquired.
Yes!
- We got him, man.
- Let's go! We got him!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
We didn't quit, brother!
We didn't quit!
All right.
Hey, nice work.
Nice work.
Good job, man.
Hey, good job. Keep looking.
...severely dehydrated...
All right, keep looking.
We're not done yet.
We are not done yet.
Give me a name.
Have we got an ID
on the subject?
What's your name, pal?
Can you hear me?
What is your name?
My name is Nick.
His name is Nick.
Repeat - subject's name is Nick.
Yes?
Oh, my God!
Oh! Oh!
Paula! He's alive!
He's alive, he's alive!
We're gonna get you
home, Nick. It's okay.
You're gonna be all right, Nick.
We're gonna get you back to your
family, buddy.
We're gonna get you home.
Thank you.
Thank you
for finding me.
Thank you for finding me.
Corey!
And stripped him,
just shy of the 30 yard line.
Marquis Cooper...
The 39 yard line,
Corey Smith.
With a tackle, Corey Smith...
...coming back
inside Bleakley.
Nicely done with the sidestep, inside.
The sole survivor, Nick
Schuyler, is here.
Welcome, Nick, to the show.
The Coast Guard
says it has found a person
clinging to an overturned boat
off Florida's Gulf Coast.
But it's not immediately clear
whether it's the same boat that
was carrying two NFL players
and two other men.
The Coast Guard has been
searching for the four men
since they were reported missing
early Sunday morning.
That's when a relative of one of
the men reported them missing.
New details
are emerging
about the remarkable search
to find Nick Schuyler
and the remarkable ways he and
three friends reportedly parted
in the rocky waters of the Gulf.
I see something.
Not sure what it is. I said,
"Have I got something?"
Everybody's eyes immediately
kind of start scanning
and picked up a pair
of binoculars
and sure enough it was a person
sitting on top of a boat.
A very dramatic
rescue this afternoon.
Schuyler was airlifted to safety
and transferred to
Tampa General Hospital
where he appeared weak
but safe,
his family, beyond relieved.
I went
and saw him first
and he told me...
"Mom, I kept saying, 'you're not
going to go to my funeral.'"
He said that's what kept him
hanging on.
Saturday, early evening
and at some point it flipped.
At some point,
the other three gentlemen
became separated
from the boat.
So but as you're sitting out
there alone...
...what did you think about,
were you scared?
I was very sad.
I kept thinking about
the guys, of course,
my family, um...
I never gave up hope.
Captions produced by
Access Media Pty Ltd